Guide to the Office of Public Affairs, Yale University, Photographs of Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Office of Public Affairs, Yale University, photographs of individuals
1870-2005
RU 686
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
53.25
The majority of the photographs in this collection were created for publicity purposes by the Office of Public Affairs.
Yale University. Office of Public Affairs
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The majority of the photographs in this collection were created for publicity purposes by the Office of Public Affairs.
Arrangement
The photographs are arranged in three series and two accessions: I. Photographs of individuals, 1870-1972; II. Photographs of individuals, 1973-1995; III. Oversize, 1978.
Photographs; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Faculty; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Officers and employees; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Students; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University -- Officers and employees; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Office of Public Affairs
- Photographs of Individuals, 1870-1972; Series I
  - Aaboe, Asgar H. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Aamodt, Gary (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abbott, Nathan (and Mrs.) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abboud, A. Robert (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Abelson, Robert P. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Abramovitz, Max (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Acheson, David (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Acheson, Dean (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Acheson, Roy M. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Achilles, Pau S. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ackerman, Bruce (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Aquistapace, James Sidney (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Adair, Robert (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Adams, Ansel (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Adams, Frederick (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Adams, Harry (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Adams, James Ring (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Adams, Jeremy Y. duQ. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Adams, John C. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Adams, Col. Louis Charles, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Adams, Norman (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Adams, Paul W. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Adams, Thornton S. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Adelberg, Edward A. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Adler, Stella (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Adriance, Walter M. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Ahern, James (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Ahlstrom, Sydney E. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Akenson, Donald H. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Albers, Josef (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Albrink, Wilhelm (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Aldrich, Malcolm P. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Alegi, Peter C. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Allderige, Clifford B. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Allen, Archibald W. (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Allen, Edward W. (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Allen, Ethan (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Allen, Greer (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Allen, Layman E. (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Allen, Phillip R. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Allen, William T. Jr. (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Alley, Nancy (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Almond, Gabriel A. (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Almond, Peter O. (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Alsop, Joseph (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Alsop, Reese Denny (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Alsop, Stewart J. O. (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Altschul, Frank (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Alvarez, Rodolfo (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Ammidon, Hoyt (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Amos, Kingsley (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Anderson, Alan R. (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Anderson, Bert G. (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Anderson, James B. (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Anderson, Priscilla Olson (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Anderson, Robert (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Anderson, Rudolf (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Adnerson, Wendell W. (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Anderson, William S. (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Andersson, Theodore (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Andrew, Richard J. (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Anex, Basil G. (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Angell, James R. (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Apter, David E. (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Archer, John Clark (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Arendt, Hanna (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Argyris, Chris (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Armour, Allison V. (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Arms, Hiram P. (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Armstrong, Richard L. (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Arnold, A. V. (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Arnold, Lauren (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Arnold, Thurman (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Arnstein, Margaret G. (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Arnstein, Mary (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Arnstein, Robert L. (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Arrom, Jose (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Asakawa, Kan-Ichi (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Ashbrook, Joseph (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Ashburn, Frank D. (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Ashley, Congressman (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Ashmole, N. Philip (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Atherton, Herbert (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Atnally, Richard (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Atterbury, Grosvenor (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Atwater, Jeremiah (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Auden, W. H. (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Audrey, Rushton L. (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Auer, Lawrence H. (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Auerbach, Erich (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Auerbach, Harry (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Auld, Frank Jr. (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Ault, Bromwell (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Austin, Edward L. (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Axeen, David Leroy (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Axelrod, Allan (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Axelrod, Joseph (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Ayer, Barbara Gay (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Ayre, Robert S. (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Baade, Eric C. (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Babb, James T. (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Babbidge, Homer D. (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Babbitt, Theodore (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Bacon, Benjamin W. (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Bacon, Francis (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Bacon, Leonard (Class of 1917) (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Bacon, Leonard (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Bacon, Selden D. (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Badser, William (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Baeta, Christian (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Bail, Louis (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Bailey, F. Lee (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Bailey, Jon Dickson (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Bailey, Latanya (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Bailey, Mark (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Baimer, F. (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Bainton, Roland H. (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Baird, Julian B. (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Baisley, Robert W. (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Baitsell, George A. (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Baker, Conrad S. (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Baker, George P. (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Baker, Howard H. (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Baker, John Thomas (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Baake, E. Wight (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Balamaci, George (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Baldrige, Malcolm, Jr. (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Baldwin, David E. (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Baldwin, Roger Sherman (Class of 1811) (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Baldwin, Roger Sherman (Class of 1845) (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Baldwin, Simeon (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Ball, George (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Ball, Stanley C. (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Balogh, Eva S. (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Banchik, Doris (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Banfield, Edward (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Banks, J. Richard (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Bannard, Otto T. (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Baratz, Merill A. (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Barber, James D. (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Barbour, William M. (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Barghoorn, Frederick C. (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Barndt, Walter D. Jr. (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Barnes, C. Tracy (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Barnes, George H. (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Barnett, Joni E. (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Barney, Samuel E. (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Barnum, Thomas R. (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Barou, Francis M. (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Barr, Browne (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Barrell, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Barrett, Jean (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Barrnett, Russell J. (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Barron, Donald (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Barrone, Donald H. (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Barry, Herbert (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Bartholomew, Marshall (Box 4, Folder 157-158)
  - Barzilauskas, Francis (Fritz) (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Barzum, Jacques (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - Basie, Count (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Bassler, John F. (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Batchelor, Malcolm C. (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Bateman, Alan M. (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Bates, James H. (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Bates, Robert C. (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Baue, Arthur E. (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Baum, Philip (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Baumer, Franklin L. (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Baumgartner, Dr. Leona (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Baumgartner, Leroy H. (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Baur, Paul V. C. (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Beach, David W. (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Beach, Frank A. (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Beach, Harlan P. (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Beach, Lewis S. (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Bean, Lee L. (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Beard, Augustus (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Beard, Rick (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Beardsley, Clifford R. (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Bechtol, Charles O. (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Beck, Fred J. (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Beck, Lloyd H. (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Becker, Christopher B. (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Becker, Edwin L. (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Becker, Russell J. (the Reverend) (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Beckwith, Isbon T. (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Beebe, William (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Beecher, Edward (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Beecher, Henry Ward (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Beers, Clifford W. (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - Beers, Henry A. (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Beeson, Paul B. (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Begle, Edward G. (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Behan, David Paul (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Beinecke, Edwin J. (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Beinecke, Frederick W. (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Beinecke, William S. (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Belafonte, Harry (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Belin, F. Lamont (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Belknap, Nuel D. (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Bell, Charles H. (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Bell, Richard H. (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Bell, Wendell (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Bell, Whitefield J., Jr. (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Belli, Melvin (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Bellinger, Alfred R. (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Bemis, Samuel Flagg (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Benda, Harry J. (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Bennett, Charles Andrew Armstrong (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Bennett, Charles H. (Box 6, Folder 212)
  - Bennett, Wendell C. (Box 6, Folder 213)
  - Bennett, William R., Jr. (Box 6, Folder 214)
  - Benson, Adolph B. (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Berdan, John M. (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - Beretta, Alessandro H. (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - Berg, Henry George (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - Berggren, Douglas C. (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Berggren, Noel D. (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Bergin, Thomas G. (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Bergman, Frances (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Bergmann, Werner (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Beringer, Edward R. (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - Beringer, Robert E. (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Berkeley, George (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Berliner, Robert W. (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Berlyn, Graeme P. (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Berner, Robert A. (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Berney, Paul R. (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - Berns, Walter F., Jr. (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - Bernstein, Ira B. (Box 7, Folder 232)
  - Bernstein, Merton C. (Box 7, Folder 233-234)
  - Bernstein, Richard J. (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - Bernstein, Thomas P. (Box 7, Folder 236)
  - Berry, Albert R. (Box 7, Folder 237)
  - Berson, Jerome A. (Box 7, Folder 238)
  - Bertino, Joseph R., M.D. (Box 7, Folder 239)
  - Berwick, Stephen A. (Box 7, Folder 240)
  - Best, Herbert W. (Box 7, Folder 241)
  - Bettleheim, Bruno (Box 7, Folder 242)
  - Bevan, Frank P. (Box 7, Folder 243)
  - Bickel, Alexander M. (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - Biddle, John C. (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - Bierwirth (Box 7, Folder 246)
  - Bigelow, Otis M. (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - Bigelow, Poultney (Box 7, Folder 248)
  - Bikel, Theodore (Box 7, Folder 249)
  - Billings, Dr. William C. (Box 7, Folder 250)
  - Binder, Henry J. (Box 7, Folder 251)
  - Bingham, Hiram (Box 7, Folder 252)
  - Bingham, Jonathon B. (Box 7, Folder 253)
  - Birney, Allan D. (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - Bishop, Carlton T. (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - Bishop, Joseph, Jr. (Box 7, Folder 256)
  - Bishop, Lottie G. (Box 7, Folder 257)
  - Bishop, Louis (Box 7, Folder 258)
  - Bishop, Walter William (Box 7, Folder 259)
  - Bishop, William H. (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Bissell, Clark (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Bitensky, Mark W. (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - Bittker, Boris I. (Box 7, Folder 263)
  - Bixler, Elizabeth (Box 7, Folder 264)
  - Black, Barbara (Box 7, Folder 265)
  - Black, Charles H., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 266)
  - Black, Charles Lund (Box 7, Folder 267)
  - Black, J. Stanley (Box 7, Folder 268)
  - Black, Lex Leroy (Box 7, Folder 269)
  - Blair, Edwin Foster (Box 7, Folder 270)
  - Blake, Francis G. (Box 7, Folder 271)
  - Blake, Whitney (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - Blalock, Hubert M. (Box 7, Folder 273)
  - Blanchette, Robert (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - Blanning, James R. (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - Blanpied, William A. (Box 7, Folder 276)
  - Blanshard, Brand (Box 7, Folder 277)
  - Blassingame, John W. (Box 7, Folder 278)
  - Blesh, Erwin T. (Box 8, Folder 279)
  - Bliss, Chester T. (Box 8, Folder 280)
  - Bliss, Harding (Box 8, Folder 281)
  - Bliss, Ray (Box 8, Folder 282)
  - Bliss, William E. (Box 8, Folder 283)
  - Blitzer, Charles (Box 8, Folder 284)
  - Bloch, Bernard (Box 8, Folder 285)
  - Bloom, Harold I. (Box 8, Folder 286)
  - Bloomer, Joseph R. (Box 8, Folder 287)
  - Bloomfield, Leonard (Box 8, Folder 288)
  - Blooston, George (Box 8, Folder 289)
  - Blough (Box 8, Folder 290)
  - Bluestein, Jeffrey L. (Box 8, Folder 291)
  - Bluhm, Beinz S. (Box 8, Folder 292)
  - Blum, John M. (Box 8, Folder 293)
  - Blum, Robert (Box 8, Folder 294)
  - Boardman, Benjamin (Box 8, Folder 295)
  - Boatwright, Howard, Jr. (Box 8, Folder 296)
  - Boaz, Joseph (Box 8, Folder 297)
  - Bockelman, Charles K. (Box 8, Folder 298)
  - Bodel, Phyllis T. (Box 8, Folder 299)
  - Boell, Edgar J. (Box 8, Folder 300)
  - Bolling, Richard (Box 8, Folder 301)
  - Boltwood, Bertram B. (Box 8, Folder 302)
  - Bondy, Philip K. (Box 8, Folder 303)
  - Bonner, David M. (Box 8, Folder 304)
  - Bonnycastle, Desmond D. (Box 8, Folder 305)
  - Bonsall, Frank F. (Box 8, Folder 306)
  - Bontemps, Arna W. (Box 8, Folder 307)
  - Bookman, Bob (Box 8, Folder 308)
  - Bookwalter, William Douglas (Box 8, Folder 309)
  - Boorch, Jean (Box 8, Folder 310)
  - Borden, John Stephen (Box 9, Folder 311)
  - Borgas (Box 9, Folder 312)
  - Borgzimer, Jan (Box 9, Folder 313)
  - Bork, Robert H. (Box 9, Folder 314)
  - Borroff, Marie (Box 9, Folder 315)
  - Bosse, Jean Pierre (Box 9, Folder 316)
  - Bossiere, Jacques P. (Box 9, Folder 317)
  - Bosworth, Thomas (Box 9, Folder 318)
  - Bouhuys, Arend (Box 9, Folder 319)
  - Boulanger, Nadia (Box 9, Folder 320)
  - Bourne, E. G. (Box 9, Folder 321)
  - Boutwell, Harvey B. (Box 9, Folder 322)
  - Bove, Joseph R. (Box 9, Folder 323)
  - Bowden, Edwin T. Jr. (Box 9, Folder 324)
  - Bowden, Joseph Jr. (Box 9, Folder 325)
  - Bowen, Vaughan T. (Box 9, Folder 326)
  - Bower, John L. (Box 9, Folder 327)
  - Bowers, A. Margaret (Box 9, Folder 328)
  - Bowles, Chester (Box 9, Folder 329)
  - Bowman, Edward H. (Box 9, Folder 330)
  - Bowman, Isaiah (Box 9, Folder 331)
  - Bowman, Ward S., Jr. (Box 9, Folder 332)
  - Boyce, John S. (Box 9, Folder 333)
  - Boyde, Malcolm (Box 9, Folder 334)
  - Boyden, James W. (Box 9, Folder 335)
  - Boyer, James L. (M.D.) (Box 9, Folder 336)
  - Boyles, ---------- (Box 9, Folder 337)
  - Bozyan, Frank (Box 9, Folder 338)
  - Braden, George D. (Box 9, Folder 339)
  - Bradferd, A. H. (Box 9, Folder 340)
  - Bradlee, Ben (Box 9, Folder 341)
  - Bradley, E. C. (Box 9, Folder 342)
  - Bradley, John (Box 9, Folder 343)
  - Bradley, Russell L. (Box 9, Folder 344)
  - Bradshaw, Lewis O. (Box 9, Folder 345)
  - Brady, Frank (Box 9, Folder 346)
  - Brady, James C. (Box 9, Folder 347)
  - Brainard, William (Box 9, Folder 348)
  - Brandenburg, Arthur (Box 9, Folder 349)
  - Brandt, Walter (Box 9, Folder 350)
  - Brantl, Virginia M. (Box 9, Folder 351)
  - Brastow, Lewis O. (Box 9, Folder 352)
  - Braudy, Leo B. (Box 9, Folder 353)
  - Braun, John E. (Box 9, Folder 354)
  - Braverman, Irwin M. (M.D.) (Box 9, Folder 355)
  - Braybooke, David (Box 9, Folder 356)
  - Breckenridge, Lester Paige (Box 9, Folder 357)
  - Breit, Gregory (Box 9, Folder 358)
  - Brennan, Paul J. (Box 9, Folder 359)
  - Brenner, Harvey M. (Box 9, Folder 360)
  - Bretton, Randolf H. (Box 9, Folder 361)
  - Brewer, David J. (Box 10, Folder 362)
  - Brewer, Fisk P. (Box 10, Folder 363)
  - Brewster, William H. (Box 10, Folder 364)
  - Brewster, Chauncey B. (Box 10, Folder 365)
  - Brewster, Connie (Box 10, Folder 366)
  - Brewster, Kingman Jr. (Box 10, Folder 367)
  - Bridgman, Walter (Box 10, Folder 368)
  - Briggs, Peter (Box 10, Folder 369)
  - Brill, Arthur S. (Box 10, Folder 370)
  - Brill, Dieter R. (Box 10, Folder 371)
  - Brinkley, Sterling (Box 10, Folder 372)
  - Brinkley, Stuart R. (Box 10, Folder 373)
  - Brinkmann, Karl (Box 10, Folder 374)
  - Briody, Bernard A., Jr. (Box 10, Folder 375)
  - Broatch, J. Wallace (Box 10, Folder 376)
  - Brobeck, John R. (Box 10, Folder 377)
  - Brock, George (Box 10, Folder 378)
  - Brodie, Bernard (Box 10, Folder 379)
  - Brogan, D. (Box 10, Folder 380)
  - Brombert, Victor H. (Box 10, Folder 381)
  - Bromley, D. Allan (Box 10, Folder 382)
  - Bronson, Francis W. (Box 10, Folder 383)
  - Bronson, William (Box 10, Folder 384)
  - Brooks, Cleanth (Box 10, Folder 385)
  - Brooks, George W. (Box 10, Folder 386)
  - Brooks, John L. (Box 10, Folder 387)
  - Brooks, Nelson H. (Box 10, Folder 388)
  - Brooks, Peter P. (Box 10, Folder 389)
  - Broude, Henry W. (Box 10, Folder 390)
  - Brouwer, Dirk (Box 10, Folder 391)
  - Browder, Felix E. (Box 11, Folder 392)
  - Brown, Charles E. (Box 11, Folder 393)
  - Brown, Charles R. (and Mrs.) (Box 11, Folder 394)
  - Brown, Frank E. (Box 11, Folder 395)
  - Brown, George A. (Box 11, Folder 396)
  - Brown, Herbert S. (Box 11, Folder 397)
  - Brown, James (Box 11, Folder 398)
  - Brown, John Mason (Box 11, Folder 399)
  - Brown, Joseph (Box 11, Folder 400)
  - Brown, Keith (Box 11, Folder 401)
  - Brown, Lowell S. (Box 11, Folder 402)
  - Brown, Mary Louise (R.N.) (Box 11, Folder 403)
  - Brown, Ralph S., Jr. (Box 11, Folder 404)
  - Brown, Robert M. (Box 11, Folder 405)
  - Brown, Roger (Box 11, Folder 406)
  - Brown, Stephen J. (Box 11, Folder 407)
  - Brown, Richmond H. (Box 11, Folder 408)
  - Brownell, Samuel M. (Box 11, Folder 409)
  - Browner, Dirk (Box 11, Folder 410)
  - Brownlee, David A. (Box 11, Folder 411)
  - Brubacher, John S. (Box 11, Folder 412)
  - Brubeck, David (Box 11, Folder 413)
  - Brumbaugh, Robert S. (Box 11, Folder 414)
  - Bruner, Jerome (Box 11, Folder 415)
  - Brush, George J. (Box 11, Folder 416-417)
  - Brustein, Norma, Robert (Box 11, Folder 418)
  - Bruton, Henry J. (Box 11, Folder 419)
  - Bryan, Kirk (Box 11, Folder 420)
  - Bryan, Robert F. (Box 11, Folder 421)
  - Bryce-Laporte, Roy S. (Box 11, Folder 422)
  - Brzezinski, Zbigniew (Box 11, Folder 423)
  - Bucher, Francois (Box 12, Folder 424)
  - Buck, Norman S. (Box 12, Folder 425)
  - Buck, Pearl (Box 12, Folder 426)
  - Buck, Sir Peter S. (Box 12, Folder 427)
  - Buckingham, William (Box 12, Folder 428)
  - Buckland, Edward G. (Box 12, Folder 429)
  - Buckley, William F. (Box 12, Folder 430)
  - Buckman, John W. (Box 12, Folder 430A)
  - Buckminster, J. (Box 12, Folder 431)
  - Buckner, Mortimer N. (Box 12, Folder 432)
  - Buder, Norman (Box 12, Folder 433)
  - Budetti, Robert P. (Box 12, Folder 434)
  - Buell, Jesse H. (Box 12, Folder 435)
  - Buendia, Jorge A. (Box 12, Folder 436)
  - Buerkle, Jack V. (Box 12, Folder 437)
  - Buesking, Albert W. (Box 12, Folder 438)
  - Buettner-Janusch, J. (Box 12, Folder 439)
  - Buffum, Imbrie (Box 12, Folder 440)
  - Buffum, Prescott C. (Box 12, Folder 441)
  - Bulkeley, E. A. (Box 12, Folder 442)
  - Bullis, W. F. (Box 12, Folder 443)
  - Bullitt, William C. (Box 12, Folder 444)
  - Bunche, Ralph (Box 12, Folder 445)
  - Bundy, McGeorge (Box 12, Folder 446)
  - Bundy, William P. (Box 12, Folder 447)
  - Bunting, Dr. Henry (Box 12, Folder 448)
  - Bunting, Mary I. (Box 12, Folder 449)
  - Burbank, Lyman B. (Box 12, Folder 450)
  - Burch, Dean (Box 12, Folder 451)
  - Burgess, John M. (Box 12, Folder 452)
  - Burgi, Richard (Box 12, Folder 453)
  - Burke, Albert E. (Box 12, Folder 454)
  - Burke, Harry (Box 12, Folder 455)
  - Burkham, James C. (Box 12, Folder 456)
  - Burkholder, Paul R. (Box 12, Folder 457)
  - Burnham, Paul S. (Box 12, Folder 458)
  - Burns, Haywood (Box 12, Folder 459)
  - Burns, James MacGrega (Box 12, Folder 460)
  - Burr, Harold S. (Box 13, Folder 461)
  - Burr, Ralph C. (Box 13, Folder 462)
  - Burrell, Ralph (Box 13, Folder 463)
  - Burrows, Millar (Box 13, Folder 464)
  - Burt, Donald McC. (Box 13, Folder 465)
  - Burton, David (Box 13, Folder 466)
  - Burton, John F., Jr. (Box 13, Folder 467)
  - Bush, Prescott (Box 13, Folder 468)
  - Bushnell, H. (Box 13, Folder 469)
  - Butler, Paul M. (Box 13, Folder 470)
  - Butler, Robert S. (Box 13, Folder 471)
  - Butt, John B. (Box 13, Folder 472)
  - Buttrey, Theodore V. (Box 13, Folder 473)
  - Butts, A. B. (Box 13, Folder 474)
  - Buxton, C. Lee (Box 13, Folder 475)
  - Buxton, Charles L. (Box 13, Folder 476)
  - Buxton, Claude E. (Box 13, Folder 477)
  - Byers, David (Box 13, Folder 478)
  - Byrd, Robert (Box 13, Folder 479)
  - Cabranes, Jose A. (Box 13, Folder 480)
  - Caccia, Harold (Box 13, Folder 481)
  - Cage, John (Box 13, Folder 482)
  - Cahill, Fred V., Jr. (Box 13, Folder 483)
  - Cahn, Michael (Box 13, Folder 484)
  - Cahoon, Herbert A. (Box 13, Folder 485)
  - Calabresi, Guido (Box 13, Folder 486)
  - Calahan, Sidney (Box 13, Folder 487)
  - Caldwell, Earl (Box 13, Folder 488)
  - Caldwell, Harry H. (Box 13, Folder 489)
  - Caldwell, Turner (Box 13, Folder 490)
  - Calhoun, --------- (Box 13, Folder 491)
  - Calhoun, John C. (Box 13, Folder 492)
  - Calhoun, Lee (Box 13, Folder 493)
  - Calhoun, Robert L. (Box 13, Folder 494)
  - Callaway, Howard H. (Box 13, Folder 495)
  - Calleo, David P. (Box 13, Folder 496)
  - Cameron, Arnold G. (Box 13, Folder 497)
  - Cameron, Norman A. (Box 13, Folder 498)
  - Camp, Charles Clark (Box 13, Folder 499)
  - Camp, Walter (Box 13, Folder 500)
  - Campbell, Alexander G. M. (Box 13, Folder 501)
  - Campbell, F. Gragory (Box 13, Folder 502)
  - Campbell, Fay (Box 13, Folder 503)
  - Campell, Thomas C. (Box 13, Folder 504)
  - Canby, Henry S. (Box 13, Folder 505)
  - Canellakis, Evangelo S. (Box 13, Folder 506)
  - Canfield, F. Curtis (Box 13, Folder 507)
  - Canham, Erwin D. (Box 13, Folder 508)
  - Cannon, Beekman C. (Box 13, Folder 509)
  - Cannon, Carl L. (Box 13, Folder 510)
  - Capizzi, Robert L. (M.D.) (Box 14, Folder 511)
  - Capp, Al (Box 14, Folder 512)
  - Cappiello, Douis (Box 14, Folder 513)
  - Capra, Paul (Box 14, Folder 514)
  - Capretz, Pierre J. (Box 14, Folder 515)
  - Capron, John D. (Box 14, Folder 516)
  - Carberry, James J. (Box 14, Folder 517)
  - Carlton, Bruce C. (Box 14, Folder 518)
  - Caro, Sona M. (Box 14, Folder 519)
  - Caroom, Hiram C. (Box 14, Folder 520)
  - Carr, Aute L. (the Reverend) (Box 14, Folder 521)
  - Carr, David T. (Box 14, Folder 522)
  - Carrington, Herbert D. (Box 14, Folder 523)
  - Carroll, Mark (Box 14, Folder 524)
  - Carroll, Richard C. (Box 14, Folder 525)
  - Carruthers, ------ (Box 14, Folder 526)
  - Carter, Elliott (Jr.) O. (Box 14, Folder 527)
  - Carter, Franklin (Box 14, Folder 528)
  - Carter, Hodding (Box 14, Folder 529)
  - Carter, Jacques F. (Box 14, Folder 530)
  - Carter, Neville L. (Box 14, Folder 531)
  - Carver, John G. (Box 14, Folder 532)
  - Casals, Jordi (Box 14, Folder 533)
  - Cash, George (Box 14, Folder 534)
  - Casper, Jonathon D. (Box 14, Folder 535)
  - Cassella, Michael (Box 14, Folder 536)
  - Cassidy, Harold G. (Box 14, Folder 537)
  - Cassirer, Ernst (Box 14, Folder 538)
  - Castles, John W. (Box 14, Folder 539)
  - Cater, S. Douglas (Box 14, Folder 540)
  - Catlin, Abijah (Box 14, Folder 541)
  - Catlin, Stanton L. (Box 14, Folder 542)
  - Cavander, Kenneth (Box 14, Folder 543)
  - Cecil, Robert M. (Box 14, Folder 544)